Zack, Arnold Arbitration Files 5512
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Bisson Inc. - Buffalo Bd. of Ed.. (Box 4)
  - Boston Edison Company and Utility Workers of America, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Boston Edison Co. and UMUA, Local 369, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boston Electrotypers Un. And N. E. Electrotype Co., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Boston Gas Co. and UMWA Dist. 50, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Boston Gas Company ATW, District 50, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Boston & Maine R.R. and Int. Bro. Locomotive Engineers, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Boston & Maine R.R. and Bro. of Railroad Trainmen, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Boston School Committee and Building Service Employees, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - British Overseas Airways Corp. and I.A.M., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - BOAC (British Overseas Airways Corps.) SBA Case No. 56-70, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The Brown Company Berlin, N.H. (and) International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Wkrs., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Ed. And Public School Adm. Assn., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Bundy Tubing - Cecil Co. Classroom Teachers Assn.. (Box 5)
  - Bundy Tubing vs. Local 1632 United Autoworkersetc. of America, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bundy Tubing vs. Local 1632 United Automobilesetc. Workers of America, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bundy Tubing vs. International Union U.A.W. Local 1632, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bundy Tubing Co. and Local 1632 UAW, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Burns International Detective Agency, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Burnham & Morrill and Am. Bakery & Confectionery Workers, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Calvert County (Md.) Bd. Of Ed. And Calvert Ed. Assoc., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cameo Curtain of New Bedford, Mass. (and) Textile Workers Union of America, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cameo Curtains of New Bedford (and) Textile Workers Union of America Case L-26484 Bos. L-4-60, 1956-1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Canada Dry Corporation Local 282 IBT, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway and Br. Railroad Trainmen, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway and Br. Railroad Trainmen Item #2, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway and Br. Railroad Trainmen Item #3, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway and BR. Railroad Trainmen Item #4, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway and Br. Railroad Trainmen Item #5, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Canadian Pacific R.R. and UTU (T) P.L.B. 502, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Canadian Pacific R.R. and UTU (T), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Canadian Pacific R.R. and UTU (T) P.L.B. 502, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Canadian Pacific R.R. and UTU (T) P.L.B. 502, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Research & Technology, Chromalloy Div. and= Amal.. Local # 475, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - CBS Television Network and Int. Un. Of Operating Engrs., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Can-Ron Inc. and U.S.W.A., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cecil County Classroom Teachers Assoc. and Cecil County Public Schools, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Chamberlain Mftg. - Colorado Springs Bd. of Ed.. (Box 6)
  - Colorado Springs Bd. Of Ed. And Teachers Association, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland Elec. Illuminating Co. -and- Local 270 - Utility Wrkrs. 5330-0079-72, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Colonial Tanning Co. Inc. and Leather Wkrs. International Union of America, Local #56, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Climber vs. Pruner, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland Elec. Illum. Co. and UWA Local 270, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Clarostat Virginia Inc. and I.U.E. Local 172, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - City Center of Music and Drama N.Y. and Stage Directors, Etc., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cincinnati Union Terminal Co., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Charles Gilman & Sons and Chauffeurs Etc. Local 59, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Charles County Bd. Of Ed., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Chapman Valve Manfg. Co. Indian Orchard, Mass. (and) IUE AFL-CIO Case No. 36648 Bos. L-247-62, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chamberlain Mfg. Corp. and U.A.W. Local 1113, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - City of New York (PERB), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Post-Hearing Memorandum on Non-Mandatory Subjects in the PSC's Proposals, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Memorandum on Issues #8 Facilities and Services, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Other Attachments, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Colorado Springs Bd. of Ed. - Courier-Citizen. (Box 7)
  - Misc., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Columbus Board of Education and Columbus Education Association, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Columbus Board of Education and Columbus Education Association, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Columbus Board of Education and Columbus Education Association, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Columbus, Ohio Bd. Of Ed. -and- Columbus Board of Education Assoc., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Columbus, Ohio Bd. Of Ed. And Columbus Ed. Assoc., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Conn. Natural Gas Corp. and Allied & Tech. Workers, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut Natural Gas Corp. and Allied & Technical Workers of U.S., Canada, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Consolidated Service Corp. and Bldg. Service Employees, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Container Corp. of Am. And Bos. Printing Specialty Un., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Contoocook Valley Teachers Assoc. and Bd. Supervisory Union 42, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Courier-Citizen and Lowell Typo. Union, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Cornish Wire Co. Williamstown, Mass. (and) IUE Local #299, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Cranston Schools - Denver Public Schools. (Box 8)
  - Cranson School Committee and Cranston Teachers Assoc., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cranston School Committee and Cranston Teachers Assoc., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cuneo Press of N.E. and Boston Printing Pressmen's and Offset Workers Union #67, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cuneo Press and Printing Pressmen's Association, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Danbury Bd. Of Education and Danbury Education Assoc., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Town of Danvers and I.A.F.F. Local 2038, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Davol, Inc. and U.R.W., Local 911, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - De Laval Tribune, Inc. and USWA, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Delaval Turbine Co. and U.S.W.A. Local 3355, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - De Laval Turbine Co. and U.S.W.A., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - De Laval Turbine Co. and U.S.W.A. Local 3355, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dee Lumber Company and Indep. Millworkers Local 7, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Delbar Products, Inc. and I.A.M., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Denny Corp. and Pulp, Sulphite Etc. #375, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Denver Public Schools and Assoc. of Special Services, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Drake Bakeries - Francis Harvey and Sons. (Box 9)
  - Francis Harvey & Sons, Inc. Worcester, Mass. (and) Carpenters Union, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - First National Stores -and- Local 592, Amal. Meatcutters Deslyn Roberts Discharge, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - First National Stores and Amalg. Meat Cutters, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - First National Stores and Amalg. Meat Cutter, Etc., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - First National Stores and Amalg. Meat Cutters, Etc., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Falmouth School Committee -and- Falmouth Educators' Assoc., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Fairfield Borough and, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - City of Everett and Everett Police Betterment Assoc., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - City of Everett -and- Everett Police Betterment Assoc., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Erie Lackawanna Rwy. And UTU (T), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Electronics Corp. of America -and- Local 272 I.U.E., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Egg Harbor Boat Co. and Teamsters Un. Local 158, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Eastern Air Lines and I.A.M. Dist. 100, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dragon Cement Company Martinsburg. West Va. (and) United Cement, Line, Gypsum Wkrs. International Union - Local 35, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Dragon Cement Company and United Cement, Lime & Gypsum Wkrs. International Union Local 26, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Drake Bakeries -and- Bakery Drivers & Salesman Gr: Wilbur Butler, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Frasse Co. - Georgia Marble Co.. (Box 10)
  - Peter A. Prasse & Co. and U.S.W.A., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - J.F. Freaney Co. and I.B.T., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - French Worsted Company and I.T.U., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Geigy Chemical Corp. and United Textile Workers, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - General Dynamics Corp. Electric Boat Div. and Carpenters, Local 1302, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - General Electric Co. and I.B.E.W. Local 3, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - General Leather Finishing and L.W.I.U. Local 21, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - General Leather Finishing Co. Salem, Mass. (and) Leather Wkrs. International Union Local #21, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - General Products Corp. and ICWU Local 192, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - General Tire & Rubber Co. Akron, Ohio U.R.W.A. Local 9, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - General Tire & Rubber Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 9, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Genetti's Super Mkts. And Amalg. Food Emp. Un. Local, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - General Tire & Rubber Co. Marion, Indiana (and) URCL & PWA Local #466, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - The Georgia Marble Co. (Green Mountain Marble Co.) United Stone & Allied Local 68, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Glens Falls - Interchem Corp.. (Box 11)
  - Glens Falls Ind. Textile Wrkrs. Un. -and- Native Textiles of Glens Falls, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Gorham Div. of Textron and Metals & Craft Union, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Grinnel Corp. and U.S.W.A., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Gulf Oil Company -and- Petroleum Trades Empls. Un., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - John Hancock Ins. Co. and Ins. Workers Intl. Union, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hill Refrigeration Div. Emhart Mfg. Corp. and U.S.W.A. Local 5298, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Hilderth Press Bristol, R.I. and Printing Pressmen, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - B.M. Hollingshead Corp. and Int. Assn. of Machinists Lodge 1, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - R.M. Hollingshead Corp. IAMAW, Local 799, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Hooker Chemical Co. -and- IAMAW, Lodge 2112, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Hume Pipe Corp. and U.S.W.A., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Huntington, L.I. Bd. Of Education + Huntington Teachers Assoc., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Huntington Teachers Assoc. and Bd. Of Education, Dist. 3, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - I.C.I. America, Inc. -and- Allied & Wrkrs, Local 12886, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Imperial Metal & Chemical Co. and U.S.W.A. No. 6291, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Ingraham Industries and I.U.E. Local 260, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Interchem. Corp. and OCAW Local 8-622, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- J. J. Corrugated Box Co. - Lexington, Town of. (Box 12)
  - Lexington Public Schools, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Town of Lexington -and- Lexington Teachers Association, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Leesona Corporation, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Leesona Corp. and I.A.M. Lodge 64, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Leesona Corp. and I.A.M., 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Lawrence Police Officers Assn. and City of Lawrence, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Lawrence General Hosp. and Mass. Nurses Assoc., 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Lakeland Fed. Of Teachers and Bd. Of Ed. Of Central Dist. No. 1, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lakeland Fed. Of Teachers and Bd. Of Ed. Of Central Sch. Dist., 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy Valve Mfg. Co. and Pattern Makers League, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy Valve Mfg. Co. and I.A.M., 1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy Valve -and- IAMAW, Lodge 31379, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - M. W. Kellogg Company and Plumbers & Pipefitters Local 461, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Kieth Fulton Company and Int'l. Bro. of Teamsters, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Keith Fulton Company and Int'l. Bro. of Teamsters, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Jones & Lamson and U.E. Local 218, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Jones & Lamson Machine Co. and U.E. local 218, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Jones Lamson Machine Co. and U.E. Local 218, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Jones & Lamson Machine Co. Springfield, Vermont (and) I.U.E. Local #218, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Jefferson Cty. Ed. Assoc. and School District R-1, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - J & J Corrugated Box Corp. and Int. Bro. Pulp, Sulphite, Etc., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Lilly Tulip Div. - Mass. Dept. of Pub. Welfare. (Box 13)
  - Lilly Tulip Div. Owens-Illinois, Inc. and I.A.M., 1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Lily-Tulip Div. of Owens Illinois and Printing Spec. Paper Products Union 470, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Perb Mediation Lindenhurst Bd. Of Educ. And Linderhurst Teachers Associations, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Lipton Pet Foods, Inc. and Sea Food Workers, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Lithographers and Photoengravers Int. Union, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Littleton Educ. Assoc. -and- Arapahoe County School Dist. #6 (Littleton, Colorado), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Lisbon School Comm. And Union #30 Teachers Assoc., 1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Long Branch Bd. Of Ed. And Long Beach Ed. Assoc., 1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - City of Lynn, Mass. And AFSCME, Local 193, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - City of Lynn, Mass. And AFSCME, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Lynn Electric Company Lynn, Mass. (and) Brotherhood of Utility Wkrs. Of N.E. Local 343, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - M. & F. Worsted Mills, Inc. Providence, R.I. (and) Textile Workers Union of Am. Case No L-23100 Bos. L-175-58, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Mack Trucks, Inc. Boston, Mass. (and) I.A.M. Lodge #1898, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Maine Central - Portland Terminal -and- Bro. of Loc. Egrs. Public Law Bd. No. 1008, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Maine Central - Portland Terminal -and- United Trans. Un. (C&T) Public Law Board No. 990, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Malden Publications, Inc. & Newspaper Guild of Boston, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Manasquan Bd. Of Ed. And M.E.A., 1970 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Manchester School Committee -and- Meachester Education Assoc., 1972 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Mapleton School Dist. -and- Mapleton fed. Of chars, (Denver Colorado), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Town of Marblehead and Local 2043 IAFF, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Marines Collids Co. and United Cement, Lime, Inc., 1968 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Marine Collids, Inc. Rockland Maine (and) Local #441, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - City of Marlboro and Firefighters, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Department of Mental Health and Mass. Mental Health Social Workers Assoc. Case No. FF-10, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Mass. Dept. of Public welfare -and- Mass. Soc. Wrkrs. Guild, Local 509, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Mass. Dept. of Public Welfare, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Mass. Inst. of Technology - New England Telephone. (Box 14)
  - M.I.T. & Research, Development & Technical Emply. Union 1130, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Mass. Inst. Of Tech. and Bldg. Service Emp., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Matawan Reg. Bd. Of Ed. And Matawan Reg. Teachers Assoc., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Metal Media, Inc. and Int'l. Union 365, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Mobil Oil Corp. -and- Maritime Local 8-801 OCAWIU, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Mobil Oil Co. and OCAWIU, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Modern Fold Co. and Newton Carpenters' Dist. Coun., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Mohawk Airlines and A.L.P.A. Case No. 788, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Morristownship, N.J. Schools and Board of Education, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Morton Shoe Stores, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Mt. Vernon Silver Co. and Metals & Craftsworkers, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Murray Brothers Tanning Co. Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Wkrs. Internationat'l Union, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Murray Leather Company Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Wkrs. International Union Local #22, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Nanuet Public Schools, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Agreement Between the Nanuet School District and the Nanuet Teachers' Association, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - National Gypsum Co. and USWA Local 5476, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - National railroad Adjustment Board Third Division, Supplemental, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - New Bedford School Comm. And New Bedford Teachers' Assoc., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - N.E. Tel. & Te. -and- I.B.E.W. Local 2222, etc., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - New Castle County Government and AFSCME Local 459, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- N.J. State Bd. of Higher Ed. - O.C.B.. (Box 15)
  - O.C.B. and AFSCME District 37, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern Airlines IAM Northwest District Lodge 143, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Northwest Airlines and A.L.P.A., 1970 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Northern Steel Inc. and U.S.W.A., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Northern Steel, Inc. Boston, Mass. (and) United Steelworkers of America, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Northern Chemical Indus. And I.C.W.U. #650, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Northern Chemical Industries, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - No. Providence School Comm. 1970 and No. Prov. Fed. Of Teachers (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Newport Finishing Corp. and Textile Workers of America, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New. Jersey State Board of Higher Ed. & Assoc. of N.J. State College Faculties, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Official Films Inc. - Philadelphia Bd. of Ed.. (Box 16)
  - In the Matter of the Employees of the School District of Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - In the Matter of the Employees of the School District of Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - In the Matter of the Employees of School District of Philadelphia, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Officials Films, Inc. and AFTRA, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Owens-Ill. Lily Tulip Cup Div. -and- Prtg. Spec. & Paper Prod. Union Local 470, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Oxford Paper Company -and- United Papermakers and workers Local 900, 1968-1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Oxford Paper Company and Un. Papermakers & Paperworks, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Pacemaker Corporation -and- International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 158, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Parkwood Laminates, Inc. Wakefield, Mass. (and) Leather Wkrs. International Union of America, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Patchogue-Medford Public Schools and Patchogue Classroom Teachers Assoc., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - J.I. Pauldings Co. and U.A.W. Local 899, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - J.I> Paulding Co. New Bedford, Mass. And, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Penn Central Trans. Co. -and- Eugene V. DiScenza, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Penn-Dixie Cement Corporation, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Penn Fruit Company -and- Retail Clerks Union, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Pennsauken, N.J. School Board, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Phenny Smidt Leather and L.W.I.U. Local 21, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Phila. Bd. Of Ed. And Phila. Fed. Of Teachers, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - School Dist. Of Philadelphia -and- Phila. Federation of Teachers, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Philadelphia Bd. of Ed.. (Box 17)
  - In the Matter of the Employees of the School District of Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - In the Matter of the Employees of the School District of Philadelphia, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - In the Matter of the Employees of the School District of Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Essays, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Philadelphia, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Detail of Proposed General Fund Operating Budget, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Philadelphia, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Fact Finder, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Philadelphia, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia Bulletin and Mag. & Nsper Handlers, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Point Pleasant Schools - RCA. (Box 18)
  - Town of Plymouth, Mass. And AFSCME, Local 41, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Point Pleasant, N.J. Schools, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Ponoganset Teachers Association Foster Glocester Reg. School, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - The Portland Company -and- Local 1256, I.A.M., 1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Port Authority-Trans Hudson Corp. and U.T.U., 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Poughkeepsie Public School System and PTA, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Providence Gravure Inc. and LPIU Local 39-P, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Providence School CTE. And Teachers' Union, Local 958, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Public Service Co. of N.H. & I.B.E.W. Local 1837, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Radio Corp. of America and I.U.E. Local 103, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Radio Corp of America and I.U.E. Local 103, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Radio Corp. of America and I.U.E. Local 103, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Radio Corp. of America and I.U.E. Local 103, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Racine Unified Sch. Dist. - Schlitz Brewing Co.. (Box 19)
  - Racine Unified Sch. Dist. Bd. -and- Racine Educ. Assoc., 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Raytheon Closed, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Raytheon Company and I.A.M. 587, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Rico Machine Company and U.S.W.A., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - John J. Riley Co. Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Wkrs. Internat'l Union Local #22, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - John J. Riley Company Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Wkrs. International Union Bernard Dever Discharge, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Rochdale Village & IUOPE, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - John A. Roebling Div. CF & I Corp. and USWA Local 3477, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Ronson Corp. and I.A.M. Local 1724, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Royal McBee Corp. Hartford, Conn. (and), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Royal Type. Co, and Royal Type. Union, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Rustcraft and Pressmens' Union and Pressmens' Union and Pressmens' Assts. Union, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - St. Mary's County- Maryland Educ. Assn., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Salem News Pub. Co. and Newspaper Guild of Salem, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Salem News Pub. Co. and Newspaper Guild of Salem, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Joseph Schlitz Brewing Co and Brewery Workers, Local 3, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Scott Paper Co. - Tauton, City of. (Box 20)
  - Scott Paper Company and Int. Bro. Pulp, Sulphite, Etc., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Seligman & Latz and N.E. Joint Board, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Sexton Can Company and U.S.W.A., District 1, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Sherwin Williams Co. John Lucas & Co. Div. and Paintmakers #1514, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Shetland Div. of Proctor Silex and IUW Local 257, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Signal Manufacturing Co. and I.U.E. Local 257, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Simmons Mattress Co. and Simmons Elizabeth Employee Union, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Smith Brothers and Teamsters, Chaffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Union, Local #379, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Sobel Industries, Inc. and I.U.E. Local 122, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - City of Somerville and Som. Municipal Emp. Assoc., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Southeastern Mass. Un. And SMU Faculty Federation, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Sou. Tel. -and- Conn. Union of Tel. Wrkrs., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Springfield Gas Light Co. and Int. Union District 50, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Southworth Machine Company -and- IAMAW Local 895 (FMCS), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - E.R. Squibb Co. and OCAW Local 8-438, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - SSEU Education Fund and New York City, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Stamina Mills Inc. Forestdale, R.I. & Tex. Wkrs. U. of Am., 1962 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Standard Thomson Corp. and I.U.E. Local 274, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Stauffer Chemical Co., Inc. and U.R.W.A. Local 367, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Stop & Shop, Inc. and Amalg. Meat Cutters, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Stowe-Woodward, Inc. and U.R.W.A. Local 525, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 21)